gametours.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy | Game Tours

  * Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**  
Last Revision: 1/16/2014

GameTours.com takes your privacy very seriously. We take your privacy seriously. We gather certain types of information about our users we want to help you to understand the terms and conditions surrounding the collection and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses the types of information we gather, how we use it, and how to correct or change it.

**Eligibility**  
Use of GameTours.com is not intended for children under the age of 13. GT prohibits registration by, and will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from, anyone under 13. This requirement will be posted at points of data collection within GameTours.com, such as registration for services.

**Information Collected**  
Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with the best and most useful content and services. We collect personally identifiable information, such as your email address and age, when you provide it to us, such as when you register on our site. Services that we offer on our sites, such as message boards, may require registration as a condition of use.

**Cookies**  
"Cookies" are pieces of information (a file) that a Web site transfers to a user's internet browser for record-keeping purposes. The use of cookies is common on the Internet. The process we use to serve advertisements and to track use of GameTours.com involves cookies. We use cookies to recognize users who have already registered on GameTours.com, allowing those users to speed up their future activities on the site. Cookies help GameTours.com track the frequency and placement of advertisements. Cookies also enable us to measure aggregate (total) usage and traffic to GameTours.com. This aids us in producing content that best meets our users' preferences. We may use that information to display advertisements that we think will be of particular interest to you. You may configure your browser to reject cookies, but this may interfere with some functionality of GameTours.com. Certain pages of GameTours.com may contain electronic images (called a "single-pixel GIF" or "web beacon") that allow a web site to count users who have visited that page. GameTours.com may occasionally use web beacons in order to count users and to recognize registered users by accessing the GameTours.com cookies.

**Information Use**

We use the information we gather for four general purposes:

\- To customize the advertising and content you see.  
\- To enhance the user experience. We use tracking information to determine how well each page performs overall based on aggregate user demographics and traffic patterns to those pages. This helps us continue to build a better service for you.  
\- To fulfill your requests for certain products and services, such as sending out electronic newsletters and enabling users to participate in polls, contests and message boards.  
\- To send you information you agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to you.

**Information Shared**

Personally identifiable information

We only make your personally identifiable information available to other companies or people when:

\- We have your consent to share the information  
\- We have engaged companies to work with us or on our behalf to provide a product or service that you have requested, such as opt-in e-mail announcements  
\- We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process; or we believe that your actions violate applicable laws, GameTours.com' Terms & Conditions or any usage guidelines for specific products or services, or threaten the rights, property, or safety of our company, our users, or others

**Updating Personal Information**

You can review, correct or change the information collected during registration by visiting your preferences page after you login. Users may change information at any time and as often as necessary.

GameTours.com reserves the right to restrict access at will to users who are perceived as being detrimental to the community.
